moomettesmagnificents.com 2017-05-31

# Privacy Statement – Moomettes Magnificents

Effective Date:  December 15, 2007

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Your privacy is important to Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet collects, and the ways in which Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet uses that personal information.

**Comment Policy:**

**Rule No. 1. It’s my blog.** As sole author of this blog, I reserve the right to edit comments that I consider are spam, offensive in nature or not family-friendly.

**Personal information collection**

Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website (including name and email address)

  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including email address)

  * information about transactions carried out over this website (including email address)

  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including name and email address)

  * any other information that you send to Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet

**Using personal information**

Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;

  * personalize the website for you;

  * enable your access to and use of the website services;

  * publish information about you on the website;

  * send to you products that you purchase;

  * supply to you services that you purchase;

  * send you statements and invoices;

  * collect payments from you; and

  * send you marketing communications.

Where Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing your data**

Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be  protected by encryption technology.

**Cross-border data transfers**

Information that Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Updating this statement**

Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Contact Moomettes Magnificents or Moomettes Crochet  
**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Moomettes Magnificents and Moomettes Crochet treatment of your personal information, please contact by email to:

###### _This privacy statement is based on a precedent created by[employmentlawcontracts.co.uk](http://www.employmentlawcontracts.co.uk/) and published by [freenetlaw.com](http://www.freenetlaw.com/)[.](http://www.freenetlaw.com/)_
